630-796-5166 junzhang@dbq.edu

## **SUMMARY**

Bilingual professional with diverse experienced in international business, freight forwarding, and sales. Familiar with air freight and transportation standards and process. Ability to organize and make arrangements speedily. Proficient in prioritizing and completing tasks in a timely manner, yet flexible to multitask when necessary.

## **EDUCATION**

Master of Business Administration

♦ Graduation Date: December 2013

University of Dubuque

Dubuque, Iowa

Bachelor of Business in International Economic and Trade

Shan Dong Foreign Language College

♦ Graduation Date: July 2012

Rizhao, China

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **Event & PR Specialist**

The Chinese Link May 2014-Present

- Assist with the setup and administration of website, including keyword research, content creation
- Develop and Execute social media campaigns, events and plans, and create and post marketing materials on Face book, Wei bo, Wechat

## **Export Coordinator**

Qingdao Good Willing International Logistics Co., LTD

January 2012-July 2012

- ♦ Handled incoming customer calls regarding coordinating cargo pick-ups, obtaining shipment information, and advising shipment status
- Performed responsibilities of preparing and reviewing shipment documentation and updating information through the export system
- Maintained continuous cooperative relationships with current clients and developed new accounts and established relationships

### **Store Owner**

Ai Ni Art Photo Studio, Qingdao, China

2012-2013

- ♦ Successfully set up online store and a merchant account to display products, manage inventory, and check out on a e-commerce platform
- Researched and analyzed market trends and identified target markets, which increased sales by 15% compared with last quarter
- Promoted the store on Alibaba, Facebook, Wechat through a discount coupon or free gift and kept the accounts up to date with new products and deals

# **ACTIVITIES AND HONORS**

Treasurer, Asian Student Union (ASU), University of Dubuque Member, Students of Color Empowerment Conference March 2013-December 2013 May 2013-December 2013

#### **SKILLS**

Fluent in English and Chinese (Mandarin)